INSTALLATIONS
- Pandas and Numpy libraries for data wrangling and processing.
- Matplotlib, Seaborn and Plotly for plotting
- Scikit Learn for predictive modelling

MOTIVATION
This analysis is the result of a wide asked question about the lack of women involvement in technology. Is it due to lack of inclusive policies within the industry? Or just a lack of interest of women on the field? After a quick research I didn´t find enoufh answers to it so it pushed me to make the present work.

FILES. The repository includes:
- A bunch of csv files containing data from StackOverFlow Annual Survey, since 2011 untill 2018.
- A jupyter notebook file written in Python containing the code used for analysis and modelling.

INTERACTION WITH THE PROJECT
This is a Data Analysis project, so probably the best way to interact with it is:
- Read first the post through the following the link:
https://medium.com/@johnmartnez_96424/how-women-will-finally-burst-in-tech-and-data-science-dc4986bb0207
- Inspect the code to find the pathways followed to find the obtained conclusions. 
- Find improvements and let me know in andresortizdeusto@gmail.com

Thanks in advance for showing interest on it!
